uaelementor.com 2019-05-02

# Privacy Policy – Ultimate Addons for Elementor

**Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used, and shared.

This privacy policy applies to all visitors, and our website users, members and customers using or accessing our websites including www.brainstormforce.com www.ultimatebeaver.com, www.uaelementor.com, convertplug.com, wpschema.com, wpportfolio.net, wpastra.com store.brainstormforce.com support.brainstormforce.com ultimate.brainstormforce.com (the “Site”).

**WHO WE ARE**

We are Brainstorm Force. you can find more information about us, including our full address, [on our company website](https://www.brainstormforce.com/contact/)

**WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

When you visit our website, we automatically collect non-personally-identifying information and personally-identifying information about your device, including information about your web browser, IP address, time zone. Additionally, as you browse the Site, we collect information about the individual web pages or products that you view, what websites or search terms referred you to the Site, and information about how you interact with the Site.

We don’t share your personal information with anyone, except to the response to a lawful request by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements or to protect our rights.

**Cookies**

“Cookies” are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. We use cookies across our sites to help identify and track visitors. Visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using our websites, with the drawback that certain features may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

**Comments**

When you leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also your IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.

An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available [here](https://automattic.com/privacy/). After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

**Contact forms**

Information submitted through the contact forms on our Site are sent to our company email, hosted by Gmail. You can find more about Google policy [here](https://policies.google.com/privacy/frameworks).

While we keep these submissions for customer service purposes and never share with any third parties.

**Support**

To help our support debug our product related issue, we might ask you to share a license key, name, email address, copy of your website, or login details with us. Since this is your website, you are the one responsible for its data and we strongly encourage you to share a staging site and remove any personal information from the database before sharing it with us.

Information submitted through the support forms on our Site is managed through Freshworks. You can find more about Freshworks policy [here](https://www.freshworks.com/privacy/).

That being said, here are some important points about what happens with the site duplicates and data that is shared with our support:

  * When a debug or setting check is needed, we ask for access to the site or even a full copy of the site.
  * We use that access/duplicates strictly for debugging.
  * We do not share that data with anyone outside of the company.
  * We cannot be held responsible for any loss of private information from databases and of your website if that should occur. We recommend that you should only share staging site or have fully working backup of whatever website you share with us.

**Purchase**

We do not store information of your credit cards and all payments are handled through payment gateways.

All direct payment gateways adhere to the standards set by PCI-DSS as managed by the PCI Security Standards Council, which is a joint effort of brands like Visa, MasterCard, American Express and Discover.

PCI-DSS requirements help ensure the secure handling of credit card information by our store and its service providers.

Additionally, when you make a purchase or attempt to make a purchase through the Site we verify your credit card through a payment gateway, and we collect certain information from you, including your name, billing address, shipping address, payment information, email address, and phone number.

If you’ve purchased our products from Envato Marketplace – we may ask you to verify your purchase through Envato APIs. Envato APIs provide us your Envato account username, email address, profile details. We also ask access to download your purchased items so we can provide automatic updates directly on your server from Envato. You can find more about Envato policy [here](https://envato.com/privacy/)

**License Keys**

To validate the purchase and to unlock benefits such as automatic updates, support from our developers and extra resources for the product offered, a licenses key is required. While activating license key, we receive your website URL, name and email address. Also we keep records of all website URLs where license key activated.

**WHO WE SHARE YOUR DATA WITH**

We don’t share, sell, trade or otherwise transfer your data with third-parties in a way as to reveal any of your personal information. However, some data is transferred and/or stored with third-party services we use to operate our websites, like Google Analytics, Google Adwords, Facebook, Easy Digital Downloads, Stripe, PayPal, Amazon SES, and Jilt.

**HOW SECURE IS MY INFORMATION**

To protect your personal information, we take reasonable precautions and follow industry best practices to make sure it is not inappropriately lost, misused, accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed.

If you provide us with your credit card information, the information is encrypted using secure socket layer technology (SSL) and stored with a AES-256 encryption. Although no method of transmission over the Internet or electronic storage is 100% secure, we follow all PCI-DSS requirements and implement additional generally accepted industry standards.

**WHAT RIGHTS YOU HAVE OVER YOUR DATA**

If want to confirm what personal data we may have about you or wish to modify it or know the purpose of the collecting and processing or to stop data sharing and processing please contact us at support@bsf.io

You can also request information about your personal data consent source (if you haven’t provided it directly to us or use our products and services) or how long it will be stored. Also, you have right to erasure, if the data is not needed for the purpose you can ask to delete the data or cease processing it. You can also request to cease using your data for direct marketing purposes. You may withdraw your consent at any time by clicking the “unsubscribe” link that can be found in our emails.

If you think we haven’t complied with data protection laws of your country, you have a right to lodge a complaint with your data protection authority. Within the technical limits, on your request, we will provide you your personal data or to your data protection authority.

If we can not provide you the requested data in a reasonable timeframe we will let you know the date when the data will be provided and if we deny your request for data we will provide a reason why we have denied the request.

**CHILDREN’S ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION ACT COMPLIANCE**

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If we determine we have collected personal information from a child younger than 13 years of age, we will take reasonable measures to remove that information from our systems. If you are under the age of 13, please do not submit any personal information through the Site, service, and Software.

**THIRD PARTY LINKS**

We may include or offer third party products or services on our website, these third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies and we do not hold any liability or responsibility for the content and activities of these linked sites.

**REMARKETING OR TARGETED ADVERTISING**

We share your Personal Information with third parties like Google Analytics, Google Adwords, Facebook, etc. to provide you with targeted advertisements or marketing communications we believe may be of interest to you. For more information about how targeted advertising works, you can visit the Network Advertising Initiative’s (“NAI”) educational page at <http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/how-does-it-work>.

You can opt out of targeted advertising by:

**NEWSLETTER EMAILS**

By becoming a Site user, member, customer of Brainstorm Force you acknowledge and agree to be signed up for our newsletter. From time to time, we may want to contact you with information about product announcements, software updates, and special offers. You may opt-out of such communications at any time by clicking the “unsubscribe” link found within the emails. We will only send marketing communications to users located in the EEA with their prior consent.

**WILL THIS PRIVACY POLICY EVER CHANGE**

We may need to update this Policy to keep pace with changes in our Site, Software, and Services, our business, and laws applicable to us and you. We will, however, always maintain our commitment to respect your privacy. we will notify you by revising the “Last Updated” date at the bottom of this Privacy Policy and, in some cases, we may provide you with additional notice (such as adding a statement to our homepage or sending you an email notification). Please note that your continued use our Site, software, and services, after any change of policy means that you agree with the new policy and consent to be bound to it.

**CONTACT US**

For more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions, or if you would like to make a complaint, please contact us by e-mail at support@bsf.io or by mail using the details provided below:

Brainstorm Force, Vasant Utsav, Opp Shell Petrol, Rajiv Gandhi Infotech Park, Hinjewadi, Pune, MH, 411057, India

**Last updated: 25 May 2018**
